Open Marvelous Designer, we can see five main windows
The one on the left is our library window
Here you can quickly call long-use files
Click the Add button to add a long-use folder for easy use
Double-click to open the clothing file
After selecting a folder, click the name again to rename the folder
Quickly double-click the folder name to open the folder
Double-click to open the virtual model
There is a history record window on the side
Single-click to open it
Click the Add button to add a history record
After selecting a history record, click the name again to rename it
Quickly double-click the history record to read the history record
After reading the history record, go back to the location of the history record and delete the current record
At the bottom left is the modular configurator
Here you can use all kinds of clothing in the library as needed and freely match
Open the folder and select the clothing you need
At the bottom window, you can see that the clothing will be divided into several parts
You can combine according to your needs
This is the 3D window, you can simulate clothing and adjust it
3D window
On the left side of the 3D window, there is a vertical map menu
Used to adjust the display settings of the 3D window
The mouse clicks on the icon, you can see all the options
For example, display clothing elements, etc.
And adjust the display style of the model, etc.
In the 2D window next to it, you can edit and adjust the clothing version
The window on the upper right is the object window
Here you can see all the materials for the clothing
For example, the button, the back of the eyes, etc.
When selecting a material in the object window
There will be corresponding attributes in the property editor at the bottom
In the property editor
You can adjust its properties according to your needs
The upper right corner can be switched to the mode
The simulation mode is used to simulate the fashion mode
The animation mode is used to create the fashion animation mode
After entering the action file, you can simulate and record the fashion animation
In the module mode, you can edit, adjust and save the fashion module
To create all kinds of clothing
The next mode is UV editor mode
In the UV editor mode, you can adjust the UV layout of the clothing
The last mode is carving mode
In the carving mode, you can use various brushes to carve the clothing
For example, use the smooth tool and click and drag the mouse on the clothing
You can make the fold of the clothing become smooth
Back to the simulation mode
At this time, the lower right corner can also change the window display button
You can select all windows or single windows according to your needs